In case you didn't know, there are
في حال لم تكن تعلم ، هناك
several Cheat Sheets on the Internet
عدة أوراق غش على الإنترنت
where you can see the runtime complexity
حيث يمكنك رؤية تعقيد وقت التشغيل
of various operations on different data
من عمليات مختلفة على بيانات مختلفة
structures. But I personally am not a fan
الهياكل. لكنني شخصيا لست من المعجبين
of these Cheat Sheets and I discourage
من أوراق الغش هذه وأنا لا أشجع
you from using this, especially if you're
من استخدام هذا ، خاصة إذا كنت
preparing for a job interview, because
التحضير لمقابلة عمل ، لأن
when it comes to data structures,
عندما يتعلق الأمر بهياكل البيانات ،
memorization doesn't work. You really
الحفظ لا يعمل. أنت حقا
need to understand the concepts, You need
تحتاج إلى فهم المفاهيم التي تحتاجها
to understand how these data structures
لفهم كيفية بناء هذه البيانات
work, how they store values, how you can
العمل ، كيف يخزنون القيم ، كيف يمكنك ذلك
perform various operations on them, and
إجراء عمليات مختلفة عليها ، و
what is the runtime. Complexity of these
ما هو وقت التشغيل. تعقيد هذه
operations. That's why I have been giving
عمليات. لهذا السبب كنت أعطي
you these exercises and asking you
لك هذه التدريبات ويسألك
questions in the middle of the videos to
الأسئلة في منتصف مقاطع الفيديو
get you involved and make you think. So
تجعلك تشارك وتجعلك تفكر. لذا
if you've been watching this course like
إذا كنت تشاهد هذه الدورة مثل
an entertaining movie, sorry, you gotta
فيلم ترفيهي ، آسف عليك
stop and go back. You should do the
توقف وارجع. يجب عليك أن تفعل
exercises before going further. Because
تمارين قبل الذهاب أبعد من ذلك. لأن
as we go through the course you're going
بينما نمضي في الدورة التدريبية التي ستذهب إليها
to learn about other types of data
للتعرف على أنواع أخرى من البيانات
structures. And if you don't understand
الهياكل. وإذا كنت لا تفهم
exactly how they work, you're not going
بالضبط كيف يعملون ، أنت لن تذهب
to be able to answer interview questions
لتتمكن من الإجابة على أسئلة المقابلة
because there's so much you have to
لأن هناك الكثير عليك
memorize and that doesn't work. So,
حفظ وهذا لا يعمل. لذا،
assuming that you have been actively
على افتراض أنك كنت نشطًا
participating, let's look at the
المشاركة ، دعونا نلقي نظرة على
differences between arrays and linked
الاختلافات بين المصفوفات والمرتبطة
lists.
القوائم.